gucu.org 2019-05-18

# Georgia United Credit Union Privacy Notice

****FACTS**  
**

| 

WHAT DOES GEORGIA UNITED CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  

---|---  
  |    
  ** **Why?**** | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  

****What?**  
**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. The information can include:

  * Social Security number and transaction history
  * Account balances and payment history
  * Credit history and credit scores

When you are _no longer_ our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
---|---  
  
****How?**  
**

|  All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information, the reasons Georgia United Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
---|---  
**Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does Georgia United  Credit Union share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?**  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes –**  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes –**  
to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | Yes   
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –**  
information about your transactions and experiences | 

No

| We don't share  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –**  
information about your creditworthiness  
| No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
**For our non-affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes  
  
| 

  * Please visit gucu.org and log into Online Banking. Select the **Services** tab, and in the drop-down menu click **Privacy Opt-Out/In**. Update your preferences and click **Submit** to save.
  * Contact us at 888.493.4328 or 770.476.6400, option 3

**Please note:**  
If you are a _new_ member, we can begin sharing your information (30) days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer_ a member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.   
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
  
---|---  
  |    
**Questions?** |  Call toll free 888.493.4328 or 770.476.6400, option 3.  
  
**Who We Are**  
  
---  
**Who is providing this notice?** | This notice is provided by Georgia United Credit Union.  
**What We Do**  
  
**How does Georgia United Credit Union  protect my personal information?** | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
**How does Georgia United Credit Union  collect my personal information?** | We collect personal information, for example, when you:  

  * Open an account or provide account information
  * Deposit money or apply for a loan
  * Use your credit or debit card

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies.  
**Why can't I limit all sharing?** | Federal law gives you the right to limit only:  

  * Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?** | Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.  
  **Definitions**  
---  
**Affiliates** | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.  

  * Georgia United Credit Union has no affiliates

**Non-Affiliates**  
| Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.  

  * Non-affiliates we share with can include insurance and broker/securities companies

**Joint Marketing** | A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.  

  * Our joint marketing partners can include insurance, broker/securities companies and other financial companies.

To download a printer-friendly version, please click here. 

Rev. 06/2018

 To protect your personal information from unauthorized access  
and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
